<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<suppressions xmlns="https://jeremylong.github.io/DependencyCheck/dependency-suppression.1.3.xsd">
  <suppress>
    <notes>
            Use of Java's default temporary directory for file creation in `FileBackedOutputStream` in Google Guava
            versions 1.0 to 31.1 on Unix systems
        </notes>
    <cve>CVE-2023-2976</cve>
    <cve>CVE-2020-8908</cve>
  </suppress>
  <suppress>
    <notes>
            Thymeleaf through 3.1.1.RELEASE, as used in spring-boot-admin (aka Spring Boot Admin) through 3.1.1 and other products
        </notes>
    <cve>CVE-2023-38286</cve>
  </suppress>
  <suppress>
    <notes>
            URL Redirection to Untrusted Site ('Open Redirect') vulnerability in FORM authentication feature Apache Tomcat.
        </notes>
    <cve>CVE-2023-41080</cve>
  </suppress>
  <suppress>
    <notes>
            Jetty is a Java based web server and servlet engine. Versions 9.4.21 through 9.4.51, 10.0.15, and 11.0.15 are vulnerable to weak authentication.
        </notes>
    <cve>CVE-2023-41900</cve>
  </suppress>
  <suppress>
    <notes>
            Eclipse Jetty Canonical Repository is the canonical repository for the Jetty project. Users of the CgiServlet with a very specific command structure may have the wrong command executed.
        </notes>
    <cve>CVE-2023-36479</cve>
  </suppress>
  <suppress>
    <notes>
            Jetty is a Java based web server and servlet engine. Prior to versions 9.4.52, 10.0.16, 11.0.16, and 12.0.1, Jetty accepts the `+` character proceeding the content-length value in a HTTP/1 header field.
        </notes>
    <cve>CVE-2023-40167</cve>
  </suppress>
  <suppress>
    <notes>
            Incomplete Cleanup vulnerability in Apache Tomcat.
        </notes>
    <cve>CVE-2023-42795</cve>
  </suppress>
  <suppress>
    <notes>
            Improper Input Validation vulnerability in Apache Tomcat.Tomcat
        </notes>
    <cve>CVE-2023-45648</cve>
  </suppress>
  <suppress>
    <notes>
            The HTTP/2 protocol allows a denial of service
        </notes>
    <cve>CVE-2023-44487</cve>
  </suppress>
  <suppress>
    <notes>
            Eclipse Jetty provides a web server and servlet container. In versions 11.0.0 through 11.0.15, 10.0.0 through 10.0.15, and 9.0.0 through 9.4.52, an integer overflow in `MetaDataBuilder.checkSize` allows for HTTP/2 HPACK header values to exceed their size limit.
        </notes>
    <cve>CVE-2023-36478</cve>
  </suppress>
  <suppress>
    <notes>
            When using the RemoteIpFilter with requests received from a reverse proxy via HTTP
        </notes>
    <cve>CVE-2023-28708</cve>
  </suppress>
  <suppress>
    <notes>
            An information disclosure vulnerability manifests when a user or an application uploads unprotected private key data as part of an authentication certificate
        </notes>
    <cve>CVE-2021-42306</cve>
  </suppress>
  <suppress>
    <notes>
            Bouncy Castle for Java before 1.73 contains a potential Denial of Service (DoS) issue within the Bouncy Castle org.bouncycastle.openssl.PEMParser class
        </notes>
    <cve>CVE-2023-33202</cve>
  </suppress>
  <suppress>
    <notes>
            In Spring Boot versions 2.7.0 - 2.7.17, 3.0.0-3.0.12 and 3.1.0-3.1.5, it is possible for a user to provide specially crafted HTTP requests that may cause a denial-of-service (DoS) condition
        </notes>
    <cve>CVE-2023-34055</cve>
  </suppress>
</suppressions>
