<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<suppressions xmlns="https://jeremylong.github.io/DependencyCheck/dependency-suppression.1.3.xsd">

    <!-- Below are the supressions added fpr False Positive CVEs -->
    <suppress until="2023-03-31">
        <notes>The CVE-2018-1258 occurs from spring security libraries, despite the latest versions are used. This is
            confirmed as false positive
            and hence it is suppressed (https://github.com/jeremylong/DependencyCheck/issues/2952).
            see (https://pivotal.io/security/cve-2018-1258)
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2018-1258</cve>
    </suppress>

    <suppress until="2023-03-31">
        <notes>These CVE's are coming from Dhowden tag library and it impacts only MP3/MP4/OGG/FLAC metadata parsing
            library. Also it is declared as false positive in
            (https://github.com/jeremylong/DependencyCheck/issues/3043)
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2020-29242</cve>
        <cve>CVE-2020-29243</cve>
        <cve>CVE-2020-29244</cve>
        <cve>CVE-2020-29245</cve>
    </suppress>

    <suppress until="2023-03-31">
        <notes><![CDATA[False positive reported for Oauth2-oidc-sdk at (https://github.com/jeremylong/DependencyCheck/issues/1658) and
            (https://github.com/jeremylong/DependencyCheck/issues/2866)]]></notes>
        <cve>CVE-2007-1651</cve>
        <cve>CVE-2007-1652</cve>
    </suppress>

    <!-- False Positive CVE supressions ends here-->

    <!-- Below are the supressions that are made for the CVEs which occur in the latest version -->
    <suppress until="2023-03-31">
        <notes>
            <![CDATA[This CVE appears in the latest version of wiremock, WireMock 2.27.2 JRE 8 embeds jquery-3.4.1.min.js. see(https://github.com/tomakehurst/wiremock/issues/1417)]]></notes>
        <cve>CVE-2020-11022</cve>
        <cve>CVE-2020-11023</cve>
    </suppress>

    <!-- Below are the supressions that are made for the CVEs which occur in the latest version -->
    <suppress until="2023-03-31">
        <notes>
            <![CDATA[This CVE appears in the latest version of jakarta]]></notes>
        <cve>CVE-2021-28170</cve>
    </suppress>

    <suppress until="2023-03-31">
        <notes>A vulnerability in all versions of Nim-lang allows unauthenticated attackers to write files to
            arbitrary directories via a crafted zip file with dot-slash characters included in the name of the
            crafted file
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2020-23171</cve>
    </suppress>

    <suppress until="2023-03-31">

        <notes>Temporary suppression
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2020-29243</cve>
        <cve>CVE-2020-29242</cve>
        <cve>CVE-2020-29245</cve>
        <cve>CVE-2020-29244</cve>
        <cve>CVE-2007-1652</cve>
        <cve>CVE-2007-1651</cve>
        <cve>CVE-2018-1258</cve>
        <cve>CVE-2022-29885</cve>
        <cve>CVE-2022-22971</cve>
        <cve>CVE-2022-22970</cve>
        <cve>CVE-2022-38749</cve>
        <cve>CVE-2022-38750</cve>
        <cve>CVE-2022-38751</cve>
    </suppress>

    <suppress until="2023-03-31">
        <notes>A vulnerability in all versions of adal4j, this library is an internal dependency in azure libraries. Hence this is suppressed</notes>
        <cve>CVE-2021-42306</cve>
    </suppress>

    <suppress until="2023-03-31">
        <notes>
            In logback version 1.2.7 and prior versions, an attacker with the required privileges to edit configurations
            files could craft a malicious configuration allowing to execute arbitrary code loaded from LDAP servers.
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2021-42550</cve>
    </suppress>

    <suppress until="2023-03-31">
        <notes>
            Need to resolve Liquibase issue before updating the library
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2022-0839</cve>
    </suppress>

    <suppress until="2023-03-31">
        <notes>
            jackson-databind before 2.13.0 allows a Java StackOverflow exception and denial of service via a large depth of nested objects.
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2020-36518</cve>
    </suppress>

    <suppress until="2023-03-31">
        <notes>
            Need to resolve Liquibase issue before updating the library
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2022-0839</cve>
    </suppress>

    <suppress until="2023-03-31">
        <notes>A Spring MVC or Spring WebFlux application running on JDK 9+ may be vulnerable to remote code execution (RCE)
            via data binding. The specific exploit requires the application to run on Tomcat as a WAR deployment. If the
            application is deployed as a Spring Boot executable jar, i.e. the default, it is not vulnerable to the exploit.
            However, the nature of the vulnerability is more general, and there may be other ways to exploit it.
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2022-22965</cve>
    </suppress>

    <suppress until="2023-03-31">
        <notes>In Spring Framework versions 5.3.0 - 5.3.16 and older unsupported versions, it is possible for a user to
            provide a specially crafted SpEL expression that may cause a denial of service condition.
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2022-22950</cve>
    </suppress>

    <suppress until="2023-03-31">
        <notes>Pivotal Spring Framework through 5.3.16 suffers from a potential remote code execution (RCE) issue if used
            for Java deserialization of untrusted data. Depending on how the library is implemented within a product, this
            issue may or not occur, and authentication may be required. NOTE: the vendor's position is that untrusted data is
            not an intended use case. The product's behavior will not be changed because some users rely on deserialization of
            trusted data.
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2016-1000027</cve>
    </suppress>

    <suppress until="2023-03-31">
        <notes>In Spring Framework versions 5.3.0 - 5.3.18, 5.2.0 - 5.2.20, and older unsupported versions, the patterns for
            disallowedFields on a DataBinder are case sensitive which means a field is not effectively protected unless it is
            listed with both upper and lower case for the first character of the field, including upper and lower case for the
            first character of all nested fields within the property path.
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2022-22968</cve>
    </suppress>

    <suppress until="2023-03-31">
        <notes>In spring framework versions prior to 5.3.20+, 5.2.22+ and old unsupported versions, applications that
            handle file uploads are vulnerable to DoS attack if they rely on data binding to set a MultipartFile or
            javax.servlet.Part to a field in a model object.
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2022-22970</cve>
    </suppress>

    <suppress until="2023-03-31">
        <notes>In spring framework versions prior to 5.3.20+, 5.2.22+ and old unsupported versions, application with a
            STOMP over WebSocket endpoint is vulnerable to a denial of service attack by an authenticated user.
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2022-22971</cve>
    </suppress>

    <suppress until="2023-03-31">
        <notes>Spring framework vulnaribilities
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2021-22044</cve>
        <cve>CVE-2020-5408</cve>
        <cve>CVE-2022-22976</cve>
        <cve>CVE-2022-22969</cve>
        <cve>CVE-2022-22978</cve>
        <cve>CVE-2021-22060</cve>
        <cve>CVE-2021-43466</cve>
    </suppress>

    <suppress until="2023-03-31">
        <notes>
            In Apache Tomcat 10.1.0-M1 to 10.1.0-M16, 10.0.0-M1 to 10.0.22, 9.0.30 to 9.0.64 and 8.5.50 to 8.5.81 the
            Form authentication example in the examples web application displayed user provided data without filtering,
            exposing a XSS vulnerability. It can looked into in the next major releases, if any latest versions released.
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2022-34305</cve>
    </suppress>

    <suppress until="2023-03-31">
        <notes>
            Versions of the Amazon AWS Apache Log4j hotpatch package before log4j-cve-2021-44228-hotpatch-1.3.5 are
            affected by a race condition that could lead to a local privilege escalation. CVE-2022-33915 occured,
            despite latest versions used.
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2022-33915</cve>
    </suppress>

    <suppress until="2023-03-31">
        <notes>
            The RipudamanKaushikDal/projects repository through 2022-04-03 on GitHub allows absolute path traversal
            because the Flask send_file function is used unsafely.
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2022-31569</cve>
    </suppress>

    <suppress until="2023-03-31">
        <notes>
            The nrlakin/homepage repository through 2017-03-06 on GitHub allows absolute path traversal because the
            Flask send_file function is used unsafely.
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2022-31548</cve>
    </suppress>

    <suppress until="2023-03-31">
        <notes>
            In Eclipse Jetty versions 9.4.0 thru 9.4.46, and 10.0.0 thru 10.0.9, and 11.0.0 thru 11.0.9 versions, the
            parsing of the authority segment of an http scheme URI, the Jetty HttpURI class improperly detects an
            invalid input as a hostname. This can lead to failures in a Proxy scenario.
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2022-2047</cve>
    </suppress>

    <suppress until="2023-03-31">
        <notes>
            In Eclipse Jetty HTTP/2 server implementation, when encountering an invalid HTTP/2 request, the error
            handling has a bug that can wind up not properly cleaning up the active connections and associated
            resources. This can lead to a Denial of Service scenario where there are no enough resources left to process
            good requests.
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2022-2048</cve>
    </suppress>

    <suppress until="2023-03-31">
        <notes>
            The PGJDBC implementation of the java.sql.ResultRow.refreshRow() method is not performing escaping of column names
            so a malicious column name that contains a statement terminator, e.g. ; could lead to SQL injection. This could
            lead to executing additional SQL commands as the application's JDBC user. User applications that do not invoke the
            ResultSet.refreshRow() method are not impacted.
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2022-31197</cve>
    </suppress>
    <suppress until="2023-03-31">
        <notes>
            The package org.yaml:snakeyaml from 0 and before 1.31 are vulnerable to
            Denial of Service (DoS) due missing to nested depth limitation for collections.
            snakeyaml v1.31 (most recent patch available currently) does not resolve the issue.
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2022-25857</cve>
        <cve>CVE-2022-38749</cve>
        <cve>CVE-2022-38750</cve>
        <cve>CVE-2022-38751</cve>
        <cve>CVE-2022-38752</cve>
    </suppress>
    <suppress until="2023-03-31">
        <notes>
          In FasterXML jackson-databind before 2.14.0-rc1, resource exhaustion can occur because of a lack of a check in
          primitive value deserializers to avoid deep wrapper array nesting,
          when the UNWRAP_SINGLE_VALUE_ARRAYS feature is enabled
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2022-42003</cve>
        <cve>CVE-2022-42004</cve>
    </suppress>
    <suppress until="2023-03-31">
        <notes>
          This apache commons text cve issue is in re-analysis and hence suppressing.
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2022-42889</cve>
        <cve>CVE-2022-42252</cve>
        <cve>CVE-2022-41854</cve>
    </suppress>
    <suppress until="2023-03-31">
        <notes>
            Postgres jdbc vulnerability is not resolved by the most recent patch 42.4.3 and is being supressed until a newer version is available.
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2022-41946</cve>
    </suppress>
    <suppress until="2023-03-31">
        <notes>
          apache commons_net
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2021-37533</cve>
    </suppress>
    <suppress until="2023-03-31">
        <notes>
            A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in fredsmith utils. This issue affects
            some unknown processing of the file screenshot_sync of the component Filename Handler. The manipulation
            leads to predictable from observable state. The name of the patch is
            dbab1b66955eeb3d76b34612b358307f5c4e3944. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The
            identifier VDB-216749 was assigned to this vulnerability.
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2021-4277</cve>
    </suppress>
    <suppress until="2023-03-31">
        <notes>
            Due to unbounded alias chasing, a maliciously crafted YAML file can cause the system to consume significant
            system resources. If parsing user input, this may be used as a denial of service vector.
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2021-4235</cve>
    </suppress>
    <suppress until="2023-03-31">
        <notes>
            Parsing malicious or large YAML documents can consume excessive amounts of CPU or memory.
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2022-3064</cve>
        <cve>CVE-2022-45143</cve>
    </suppress>
    <!-- Supression Group ends here -->
</suppressions>
