<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<suppressions xmlns="https://jeremylong.github.io/DependencyCheck/dependency-suppression.1.3.xsd">

    <!-- Below are the supressions added fpr False Positive CVEs -->

    <!-- New Supressions for June  -->
    <suppress until="2023-10-30">
        <notes>
            Postgres version 42.2.27 in combination with jackson-databind has interface changes in DBUtils that cause unit tests to fail.
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2022-21724</cve>
    </suppress>
    <suppress until="2023-10-30">
        <notes>
            spring-webmvc version 5.3.26 casues issues that fail unit test cases due it not being able to create test environment correctly.
            Likely will need tests to be re-written when upgrading due to interface change.
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2022-22965</cve>
        <cve>CVE-2021-22118</cve>
        <cve>CVE-2022-22950</cve>
        <cve>CVE-2022-22971</cve>
        <cve>CVE-2022-22968</cve>
        <cve>CVE-2022-22970</cve>
        <cve>CVE-2021-22060</cve>
        <cve>CVE-2021-22096</cve>
        <cve>CVE-2023-20861</cve>
        <cve>CVE-2021-22044</cve>
        <cve>CVE-2022-22969</cve>
    </suppress>
    <suppress until="2024-03-31">
        <notes>
            adal4j version 1.3.0 in combination with jackson-databind has interface changes in DBUtils that cause unit tests to fail.
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2021-42306</cve>
    </suppress>
    <suppress until="2024-01-31">
        <notes>
            liquibase-core version 3.8.9 in combination with jackson-databind has interface changes in DBUtils that cause unit tests to fail.
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2022-0839</cve>
    </suppress>
    <suppress until="2024-01-31">
        <notes>
            commons-fileupload-core version 1.4 in combination with jackson-databind has interface changes in DBUtils that cause unit tests to fail.
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2023-24998</cve>
    </suppress>
    <suppress until="2024-01-31">
        <notes>
            commons-text version 1.7 in combination with jackson-databind has interface changes in DBUtils that cause unit tests to fail.
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2022-42889</cve>
    </suppress>
    <suppress until="2024-01-31">
        <notes>
            handlebars version 4.2.1 in combination with jackson-databind has interface changes in DBUtils that cause unit tests to fail.
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2022-42889</cve>
    </suppress>
    <suppress until="2024-01-31">
        <notes>
            jackson-core version 2.12.7 in combination with jackson-databind has interface changes in DBUtils that cause unit tests to fail.
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2022-45688</cve>
    </suppress>
    <suppress until="2024-01-31">
        <notes>
            json-path version 2.4.0 in combination with jackson-databind has interface changes in DBUtils that cause unit tests to fail.
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2022-45688</cve>
    </suppress>
    <suppress until="2024-01-31">
        <notes>
            json-path version 2.4.0 in combination with jackson-databind has interface changes in DBUtils that cause unit tests to fail.
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2022-45688</cve>
    </suppress>
    <suppress until="2024-01-31">
        <notes>
            json-smart version 2.4.10 in combination with jackson-databind has interface changes in DBUtils that cause unit tests to fail.
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2022-45688</cve>
        <cve>CVE-2023-35116</cve>
    </suppress>
    <suppress until="2024-01-31">
        <notes>
            postgresql version 2.4.10 in combination with jackson-databind has interface changes in DBUtils that cause unit tests to fail.
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2022-45688</cve>
    </suppress>
    <suppress until="2024-03-31">
        <notes>
            Postgres version 42.4.18 in combination with jackson-databind has interface changes in DBUtils that cause unit tests to fail.
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2022-31197</cve>
        <cve>CVE-2022-41946</cve>
    </suppress>
    <suppress until="2024-01-31">
        <notes>
            snakeyaml version 1.32 in combination with jackson-databind has interface changes in DBUtils that cause unit tests to fail.
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2022-1471</cve>
    </suppress>
    <suppress until="2024-01-31">
        <notes>
            spring-cloud-netflix-archaius version 2.0.4.RELEASE in combination with jackson-databind has interface changes in DBUtils that cause unit tests to fail.
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2020-5412</cve>
    </suppress>
    <suppress until="2024-01-31">
        <notes>
            spring-cloud-netflix-core version 2.0.4.RELEASE in combination with jackson-databind has interface changes in DBUtils that cause unit tests to fail.
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2020-5412</cve>
    </suppress>
    <suppress until="2024-01-31">
        <notes>
            spring-cloud-netflix-ribbon version 2.0.4.RELEASE in combination with jackson-databind has interface changes in DBUtils that cause unit tests to fail.
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2020-5412</cve>
    </suppress>
    <suppress until="2024-01-31">
        <notes>
            spring-cloud-starter-netflix-archaius version 2.0.4.RELEASE in combination with jackson-databind has interface changes in DBUtils that cause unit tests to fail.
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2020-5412</cve>
    </suppress>
    <suppress until="2024-01-31">
        <notes>
            spring-cloud-starter-netflix-hystrix version 2.0.4.RELEASE in combination with jackson-databind has interface changes in DBUtils that cause unit tests to fail.
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2020-5412</cve>
    </suppress>
    <suppress until="2024-01-31">
        <notes>
            spring-security-config version 5.4.11 in combination with jackson-databind has interface changes in DBUtils that cause unit tests to fail.
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2022-22978</cve>
        <cve>CVE-2022-22976</cve>
    </suppress>
    <suppress until="2024-01-31">
        <notes>
            spring-security-crypto version 5.4.11 in combination with jackson-databind has interface changes in DBUtils that cause unit tests to fail.
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2022-22978</cve>
        <cve>CVE-2022-22976</cve>
    </suppress>
    <suppress until="2024-01-31">
        <notes>
            spring-security-web version 5.4.11 in combination with jackson-databind has interface changes in DBUtils that cause unit tests to fail.
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2022-22978</cve>
        <cve>CVE-2022-22976</cve>
    </suppress>
    <suppress until="2024-03-31">
        <notes>
            tomcat-embed-core version 9.0.73'in combination with jackson-databind has interface changes in DBUtils that cause unit tests to fail.
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2023-28708</cve>
        <cve>CVE-2023-34055</cve>
        <cve>CVE-2023-33202</cve>
        <cve>CVE-2023-46589</cve>
    </suppress>
    <suppress until="2024-01-31">
        <notes>
            commons-fileupload need major version upgrade.
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2023-24998</cve>
    </suppress>
    <suppress until="2024-01-31">
        <notes>
            Jackson core needs major version latest 2.12.7  not resolving current CVE issue. Same applies to json-path version 2.4.0.
            Same applies to json-smart version 2.4.10
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2022-45688</cve>
    </suppress>
    <suppress until="2024-01-31">
        <notes>
            Jackson-databind version 2.12.7.1 in combination with postgres has interface changes in DBUtils that cause unit tests to fail.
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2020-36518</cve>
        <cve>CVE-2022-42003</cve>
        <cve>CVE-2022-42004</cve>
        <cve>CVE-2023-20863</cve>
    </suppress>
    <suppress>
        <notes>SnakeYaml's Constructor() class does not restrict types which can be instantiated during deserialization.
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2022-1471</cve>
    </suppress>
    <suppress>
        <notes>In spring framework versions prior to 5.2.24 release+ ,5.3.27+ and 6.0.8+ , it is possible for a user to provide a specially crafted SpEL expression that may cause a denial-of-service (DoS) condition.
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2023-20863</cve>
    </suppress>
    <suppress>
        <notes>Pay is a payments engine for Ruby on Rails 6.0. In versions prior to 6.3.2 a payments info page of Pay is susceptible to reflected Cross-site scripting.
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2023-30614</cve>
    </suppress>
    <suppress>
        <notes>
            jackson-databind 2.10.x through 2.12.x before 2.12.6 and 2.13.x before 2.13.1 allows attackers to cause a denial of service (2 GB transient heap usage per read) in uncommon situations involving JsonNode JDK serialization.
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2021-46877</cve>
    </suppress>
    <suppress until="2030-10-30">
        <notes>
            Spring boot requires version update beyond current version range
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2023-20883</cve>
    </suppress>
    <suppress>
        <cve>CVE-2023-35116</cve>
    </suppress>

    <suppress>
        <notes>
            Use of Java's default temporary directory for file creation in `FileBackedOutputStream` in Google Guava
            versions 1.0 to 31.1 on Unix systems
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2023-2976</cve>
        <cve>CVE-2020-8908</cve>
    </suppress>
    <suppress>
        <notes>
            Reactive web applications that use Spring HATEOAS to produce hypermedia-based responses might be exposed to malicious forwarded
            headers if they are not behind a trusted proxy that ensures correctness of such headers, or if they don't have anything else in
            place to handle (and possibly discard) forwarded headers either in WebFlux or at the level of the underlying HTTP server.
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2023-34036</cve>
    </suppress>
    <suppress>
        <notes>
            Thymeleaf through 3.1.1.RELEASE, as used in spring-boot-admin (aka Spring Boot Admin) through 3.1.1 and other products
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2023-38286</cve>
    </suppress>
    <suppress>
        <notes>
            Using "**" as a pattern in Spring Security configuration for WebFlux creates a mismatch in pattern matching between Spring Security and Spring WebFlux, and the potential for a security bypass.
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2023-34034</cve>
    </suppress>
    <suppress>
        <notes>
            URL Redirection to Untrusted Site ('Open Redirect') vulnerability in FORM authentication feature Apache Tomcat.
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2023-41080</cve>
    </suppress>
    <suppress>
        <notes>
            Jetty is a Java based web server and servlet engine. Versions 9.4.21 through 9.4.51, 10.0.15, and 11.0.15 are vulnerable to weak authentication.
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2023-41900</cve>
    </suppress>
    <suppress>
        <notes>
            Eclipse Jetty Canonical Repository is the canonical repository for the Jetty project. Users of the CgiServlet with a very specific command structure may have the wrong command executed.
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2023-36479</cve>
    </suppress>
    <suppress>
        <notes>
            Jetty is a Java based web server and servlet engine. Prior to versions 9.4.52, 10.0.16, 11.0.16, and 12.0.1, Jetty accepts the `+` character proceeding the content-length value in a HTTP/1 header field.
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2023-40167</cve>
    </suppress>

    <suppress>
        <notes>
            A batch loader function in Spring for GraphQL versions 1.1.0 - 1.1.5 and 1.2.0 - 1.2.2 may be exposed
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2023-34047</cve>
    </suppress>
    <suppress>
        <notes>
            Incomplete Cleanup vulnerability in Apache Tomcat.
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2023-42795</cve>
    </suppress>
    <suppress>
        <notes>
            Improper Input Validation vulnerability in Apache Tomcat.Tomcat
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2023-45648</cve>
    </suppress>
    <suppress>
        <notes>
            The HTTP/2 protocol allows a denial of service
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2023-44487</cve>
    </suppress>

    <suppress>
        <notes>
            jackson-databind before 2.13.0 allows a Java StackOverflow exception and denial of service via a large depth of nested objects.
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2020-36518</cve>
    </suppress>
    <suppress>
        <notes>
            Apache Commons Text performs variable interpolation, allowing properties to be dynamically evaluated and expanded.
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2022-42889</cve>
    </suppress>
    <suppress>
        <notes>
            Eclipse Jetty provides a web server and servlet container. In versions 11.0.0 through 11.0.15, 10.0.0 through 10.0.15, and 9.0.0 through 9.4.52, an integer overflow in `MetaDataBuilder.checkSize` allows for HTTP/2 HPACK header values to exceed their size limit.
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2023-36478</cve>
    </suppress>
    <suppress>
        <notes>
            In FasterXML jackson-databind before 2.14.0-rc1, resource exhaustion can occur because of a lack of a check in primitive value deserializers to avoid deep wrapper array nesting
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2022-42003</cve>
        <cve>CVE-2022-42004</cve>
    </suppress>

    <suppress>
        <notes>
            When using the RemoteIpFilter with requests received from a reverse proxy via HTTP
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2023-28708</cve>
    </suppress>

    <suppress>
        <notes>
            Improper Restriction of XML External Entity Reference in GitHub repository liquibase/liquibase prior to 4.8.0.
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2022-0839</cve>
    </suppress>

    <suppress>
        <notes>
            PostgreSQL JDBC Driver (PgJDBC for short) allows Java programs to connect to a PostgreSQL database using standard, database independent Java code.
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2022-31197</cve>
    </suppress>

    <suppress>
        <notes>
            PostgreSQL JDBC Driver (PgJDBC for short) allows Java programs to connect to a PostgreSQL database using standard, database independent Java code.
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2022-31197</cve>
    </suppress>
    <suppress>
        <notes>
            A serialization vulnerability in logback receiver component part of logback version 1.4.11 allows an attacker to mount a Denial-Of-Service attack by sending poisoned data.
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2023-6378</cve>
    </suppress>

    <!-- Supression Group ends here -->
</suppressions>
